Made in ABC
Ren!
Good morning.
Are you alive?
Yes, I am.
Good morning.
Well...
Sawaiya-san hasn't come yet.
Not yet.
He's a great test subject.
What?
No, Okido-kun, what's wrong?
He's a boxing player.
What?
Hey you, are you late for the test?
I'm sorry.
Hurry up!
Good morning.
Sawaiya...
As usual, you have a good sense of humor.
Let's get started.
Good morning.
Don't talk.
We're in the middle of a test.
Come on.
Let's get started.
Okay, that's enough.
Don't stop.
If you like it, I'll give it to you.
Come on, let's get started.
Okay.
Sawaiya-san.
There are some tests that I haven't taken yet, but...
It's okay now.
No, it's not okay.
You have to take the test.
It doesn't matter how many points I get.
I looked up a lot about the scholarship.
Do you have time after this?
Sensei, really.
Don't use your time for me.
I couldn't help but give up, so I came here.
Please go out with me.
Okay.
Let's go out.
Really?
What should I do?
Thank you.
Hey, seriously.
Two years of Komina and Masa.
That's right.
I didn't expect you to say okay.
What? What do you mean?
Honda-kun.
What?
Can I talk about my situation?
It's okay, but you do it.
Miyasaka-kun.
Minamina-kun is the captain of the soccer club.
He practices every day.
Is that so?
When you work on one thing, you can understand a woman's heart.
That's right.
Rena, Rena.
Did you hear that?
A girl of the second year asked Kengo out and he said okay.
That's amazing.
Here it comes.
That's right.
Kengo.
What do you mean?
Why did you close it?
I don't know your face.
Just imagine.
I don't imagine.
I'll tell you in detail.
I'll take it.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm not going home yet.
I have to prepare for class and take the test.
The summer vacation of the basketball club.
I haven't submitted the documents to the prefectural government.
You should have taken a little more time to prepare for class.
Wait a minute.
What?
Recently, I've been doing well.
It's a good game.
Dagajun is a barbecue shop where soccer players gather.
I haven't been there recently.
Is it okay to go with me?
I'm so happy.
Let's go.
Senpai.
Can I hold your hand?
Okay.
Let's go.
He's the famous claimant, right?
Yes.
A vacation?
What is this?
Hello.
You finally came out.
What?
I'm back.
I want to see you again.
Can you give me a chance?
What is this?
Do you know what this means?
You crushed it.
The result was really crushed.
So what?
It's as I said.
Can you take responsibility?
I can't take responsibility.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Don't hit Ringo.
He's the one who hit me.
Right?
That's right.
If you're going to complain, it's that claimant's uncle.
But it's true that I said something great.
I'm really sorry.
Kengo, what are you crying about?
Because...
He's a big guy and a small guy.
He's a girl.
Everyone, sorry for the sudden meeting.
I think there are a lot of teachers who are already listening.
This is the claimant, Shinmatsu.
It's closed at the end of the month.
That's right.
I think it's one of the major factors that the students in this school are no longer able to go to the store.
Excuse me, can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
Mr. Okuma, please.
Does that mean that our school may be held responsible?
There is a possibility if the claimant comes.
Just in case, I contacted the school lawyer and confirmed it.
From now on, please do not actively act.
What does that mean?
I'm sorry.
It's because of our school that the number of customers has decreased.
That's right.
Why?
It's actually true.
If you think so, you should take responsibility.
Don't apologize because you may lose in the trial.
In the first place, the school lawyer is a lawyer.
That's right.
Has the school become an era in which lawyers are hired?
What's wrong with you?
Dad, you drank too much.
Dad, you're drunk.
But if you tell the lawyer not to do anything, you won't be able to do anything.
Still, I want to apologize to you.
I understand how you feel.
If you understand.
But as a school policy.
I feel like I'm a human being before the court says what to do.
But if you actually become a judge and get a lot of money from Dagajun, can you take responsibility?
I won't.
I won't do anything like a trial or a fine.
You don't understand.
If it's for the sake of money, it's normal to twist justice or faith.
It's noisy.
It's not noisy.
What's wrong with apologizing?
I understand how you feel.
Everyone, be quiet.
Be quiet for a moment.
Ringo.
Hey.
Mr. Yoshida.
Yes, hello.
No, no.
Yes, I'm here.
Yes.
The president of the other day?
Really?
No, I'm happy.
I'm waiting.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hey, is that man coming?
Come on, take me to the president.
Hey, hey, hey.
Wait a minute.
Did something happen after Mr. Yoshida sent you the other day?
You were late to go home, weren't you?
Are you okay?
Do it well.
Damn it.
After all, she's my daughter.
What are you looking for?
My cell phone.
Your cell phone.
If that man comes, I'll go up.
What?
Get out of the way.
Hey, hey.
Hey, I said I was here.
Reina, wait a minute.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Nice.
I'm happy.
I'm really excited.
Wait a minute.
Don't rush.
It's okay.
I didn't get anything.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
Hey, isn't it really bad?
I said that I am going to high school.
You said you are going to high school
But really?
I'm serious.
Hey, hey, hey.
You knew that, didn't you?
Get fired up, seriously.
Hey, where's the shower?
It's okay.
It's not okay.
Please.
I see.
Then let's go together.
I'm embarrassed.
Okay.
I'll be right out.
Hey, you're not here?
I'm sorry.
But it's an honor to have the president come again.
What?
I heard you were here.
I'm sorry.
I haven't been able to reply to you in a long time.
You haven't contacted me at all.
You haven't contacted me.
It's not that.
It's Lena.
Teacher.
You shouldn't touch Lena.
What if I touch her?
Hey, teacher.
Are you serious?
Huh?
You're not a minor, are you?
It doesn't matter if you love her or not.
But don't play with her too much.
I'm the one who's being played with.
What do you mean?
Okay.
Huh?
No way.
I'll go.
Don't yell at me, old pervert
Hey.
Are you sure you don't feel bad?
Making love with a high school student
You said high school student.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Sawaiya!
Huh?
What are you doing?
I'm going home.
Is your house this way?
I'm meeting up with my club mates.
I see.
What are you doing at this hour?
I'm going home.
I see.
Hey.
What?
Come with me
I'm a lone girl, it's scary
To walk at night.
Okay.
You're practicing at night.
That's amazing.
We don't have club activities every day.
Do you think you can go to the national competition?
No.
I don't know.
I want to go though.
It's not the time to make a girlfriend.
She's only in second grade?
Yeah.
She's really cute.
You look great.
Yeah.
Really?
It's over there.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Bye.
Good night.
Hey
What is it?
Well... You know...
Don't hang out with that old man at night.
What?
I'm going home.
Thank you.
Oh, Frank.
You're a great politician.
Well, well, well.
I need to go to the toilet.
Wait.
That guy.
I can't stop.
Rio.
Are you asleep?
I'm coming in.
Rio.
Hey, Rio.
Are you okay?
Go to bed.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Miyasutako.
Did you buy a guitar?
It's better to be able to play the guitar.
You're right.
Hey, Rio.
Even if you go to Yamamoto-kun's house...
I'm sure you'll get kicked out.
I have no choice but to do this.
I'm sorry.
I told you to spread it.
That guy.
Hurry up.
I wonder if he's doing something that doesn't make sense.
It's raining.
What kind of band is it?
Hello.
Hello, Rio-sensei.
Hello, Miyasutako.
I remembered.
I have a question.
What is it?
What kind of music do you like?
Me?
What kind of band do you like?
I don't have a particular one.
But I like rock music.
Rock?
What kind of music do you like?
I don't know.
I don't listen to music.
Really?
I don't know.
I'm surprised.
Do you know how Soseki Natsume played the role of I love you?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Does anyone know?
I know.
You played the role of the moon is beautiful.
Yes.
Do you know that?
I've heard this before.
This is a urban legend that I don't know if it's true or not.
Soseki was teaching English.
At that time, the student played the role of I love you.
Soseki Natsume said that the Japanese don't say it directly.
He played the role of the moon is beautiful.
He said that.
I'm so emotional just because I don't say it directly.
You're right.
There are some phrases that say the moon is beautiful.
If it was you, how would you respond?
I'm tired.
The next day.
I want to play a band with you.
You want to play a band with me?
I'll open the door.
Brother.
Jinsu.
I heard you're going to play a band again.
I was invited by Miyasaka.
Hello.
What kind of band are you going to play?
Rock.
Are you a guitarist?
I just started.
I see.
All rock guitarists have a saying,
Let's start from the purple.
Do you know?
I don't know.
Is it a saying?
Is it a revolution?
That's right.
The most important thing to do when you want to play rock.
It's here.
Do your best.
I'll go to my part time work
What's purple?
The law of our house.
Vibe.
Deep purple.
Don't spread out.
It's dangerous.
Hey.
Wait.
Hey, old man.
What?
Do you know?
Do you know the Monjayaki store in Shinmatsu?
It's closing at the end of this month.
I know.
Do you know?
Do you know that the old man will be crushed?
Do I have to follow the rules?
Yes, you have to!
What did you say?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Please come in.
Excuse me.
Director.
What's with that hurt face?
Excuse me.
I'm not doing all the work.
I'm doing it sometimes.
Did you hear about it?
Yes, I heard from Mr. Kimoto.
Kengo.
Why are you so...
I can't accept it.
I understand how you feel.
The other person is a claimer.
That's right.
But...
That person is called Izumi-san.
I understand that everyone is quiet.
But that person has his own justice.
I think what he said is right.
But isn't he too harsh?
Well, yes, probably.
If there's a problem with the person who can't sue,
shouldn't that old man sue?
I think...
There must be a reason
What's the reason for being a claimer?
The cause is not our students.
Izumi-san's wife had a car accident.
But Izumi-san's wife had a car accident.
What?
A bike in the middle of school?
Is that so.
Was it about 10 years ago?
About that...
I didn't know about it either.
At school, the bikes were being ran.
His wife...
She tried to avoid the bikes
who were being run at high speed.
She ran into the boys' high school.
Her spine was damaged.
She was living a life with no-sense.
Could it be that you still do?
It seems so.
After that, Ms. Izumi didn't complain about the students or the school.
Instead, he complained to the school that had a lot on her mind.
The hospital she was admitted to was the Taisei Hospital.
He was very concerned about her health.
I think Ms. Izumi's constant complaints are from the feeling that
I think it's from the feeling that he doesn't want the students to become victims or victims.
There's a reason behind human behavior.
Even if you think you're a victim.
It's very important that you don't decide what he's doing or what he's doing.
It's very important that you try to face him.
It's like a morning bath.
It's important to know.
It's important to know how to move.
There's a reason behind it.
It's because there's a reason why he's doing such a terrible thing.
It's a family problem.
Are you talking about my students?
No, it's just an example.
Are you talking about someone who's terrible?
No, it's nothing like that.
But I don't want it to end like this.
Senpai!
Ouch!
I'm sorry. What is it?
It's nothing.
You're not listening to me at all.
I'm sorry.
There's a lot going on.
It's okay.
It's not good.
But I don't want it.
It's okay.
It's not good.
Listen to me.
Okay.
Cheers.
Good evening.
Welcome.
What should I do?
Here you go.
Thank you.
The usual?
Yes.
What about you?
Mochi cheese mentaiko.
That's the most popular one.
It's popular.
And orange juice, please.
Okay.
Ochi-chan.
Yes?
Are you really going to quit next week?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I should have walked.
It's just the timing.
It's not Minamida's fault.
But...
Due to the coronavirus,
the number of customers has decreased.
We were able to make some money.
I'm sorry.
It's not like that.
It's just the timing.
We were looking for a job.
We're getting old.
It's true.
It's all thanks to you.
Especially the soccer club.
Yes.
It's all thanks to you.
You've been with us for a long time.
You've loved our shop.
You've done so much for us.
We can't help to be grateful.
Right?
You're right.
Here you go.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Minamida, thank you for coming all the way here.
You're welcome.
I'm so happy.
Really, me and this old granny.
Right?
You're the captain of the traditional soccer club.
Rio.
What's wrong?
On the last day of the month,
all the soccer clubs gather.
Don't you want to go out?
When?
On the last day of the month, Saturday
Saturday?
I don't feel like going,
but that day...
I see.
I want you to come because it's the last day.
I won't force you.
Mr. Tsubakana's original goods are on sale.
Angel and devil figures in the play.
Key holder.
The pouch I designed.
Clear Wild Mall.
More information on the show's website.
This cushion is on sale.
What?
They're here.
My friends are here.
Ringo, what are you doing?
I'm helping them.
They're going to have a hard day.
I don't need a part-time job, so I'm helping them.
What are you doing?
Hey, Keiko.
Hey.
Hello.
Hey, Oji.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
You're amazing today.
Look at this.
Hello.
I'm helping them.
You're helping them?
Yes.
Really?
Hurry up.
You're so dirty, Mochizuki.
Mochizuki.
I'm with you.
Take your time.
I miss you.
Hey.
Did you know Dagashi was the last one?
Look, it's TikTok.
Sorry.
We did it on our own.
It looks like the Obis saw this and contacted us.
It's over there.
Genki.
Yes.
Where's the captain?
I'm here.
You're the captain?
Yes.
At the end of the day, let's give a big thanks to Dagashin.
Genki.
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
It's been a while.
This is a souvenir from America.
I'm glad you came.
I sent you a few messages, but they didn't come to mind.
I wanted to write all my honest and sincere feelings.
I'm afraid to see you.
I'm afraid to talk to you.
So I'm afraid to look at my phone.
Afraid, why?
I thought I'd forgive you for everything.
When I saw your face,
I thought I'd start a new relationship with you.
Really?
It was a life I could only think of you.
I'm so happy.
No matter how many things I've done, it's always been like that.
I've always been like that.
But I'm sorry.
Oh, I don't have to say sorry.
I don't feel that way right now.
That's right.
When I saw your face, I felt like I'd forgive you for everything.
There's a place I want to go now.
I didn't mean to go at all.
Maybe it's going to stop here.
And I expected it to come back to life.
I'm surprised at myself now.
I'm glad you came to Seiya.
It was a perfect place to stop.
I'm going.
The place I want to go is not here.
Are you talking about another man?
Did you make another man you like?
I haven't made a man I like.
Then...
But I made a lot of important people.
I made a lot of people I had to value.
Students?
Yeah.
I can't afford to be stressed out about my relationship with you anymore.
I'm full of them.
So...
Let's end it.
I can't accept it.
Accept it?
It's your own responsibility.
Then...
Hey.
It's okay.
Just wait.
Thank you for all the mistakes you've made.
Can I have this?
Sure.
You were here?
Come in.
What an amazing person.
Everyone, Rio-chan is here.
Hello.
Rio-chan.
Rio-chan, you're here.
Sorry I'm late.
Not at all. Thank you.
This person...
Rio-chan, my teacher.
Hello.
I'm Sasaoka, I'm in charge of Minamida-kun.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's so good.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm so glad.
It tastes the same.
It's good, right?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Are you really her teacher?
Yes.
I'm her teacher.
I don't know if she's a teacher or not.
Thank you.
She's so good.
Hey, hey, hey.
Did you hear that?
Yes.
Did you go to the national contest?
Yeah.
Kono?
It's Fukumon.
Well, you are a supplementary student.
I thought you were a good student.
Lastly, I'd like to ask you two to say hello.
Tonight,
Thanks to all of you, I was able to see everyone's faces for the first time in a long time.
It was a time-slip.
At that time, I was able to do business in this house for more than 50 years.
There were a lot of good things, and a lot of bad things.
But thanks to all of you, I was able to change everything into a good feeling.
Thank you. Thanks to all of you.
In that sense, I have a request to all of you.
Please don't blame anyone for this closing.
Please.
It's our decision. So it's not anyone's fault.
Thanks to all of you, we were really happy.
And it was the best ending.
Thank you all.
Thank you.
Thank you, aunt.
Ringo.
Thank you.
Oh no.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to get you some water?
No.
I'm sorry.
Should I call an ambulance?
Sasaoka-san, how are you?
I feel much better now.
Please don't get up yet.
I'm sorry.
Sasaoka-san, I'm going to remove the ceiling.
Yes.
I think I have something to talk to the teacher.
What?
I have something to talk to the teacher.
I can't believe it.
Excuse me.
Please come in.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
I wonder what it is.
You're getting pregnant.
What?
Congratulations.
So there's no medicine today.